<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ice&#39;s Corner</title>
    <link>https://rdseed.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ice&#39;s Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://rdseed.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/notes/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/notes/notes/</guid>
      <description> PPM File Format for images </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>c8fontgen Link to heading c8fontgen is a tiny pixel editor written in pure C using raylib, and raygui. It is very minimal in functionality and was mostly created to test out the capabilities of the previously stated libraries. A self contained executable for linux based system exists for it in the releases section for you to try out.&#xA;dy-chip8-reborn Link to heading It is an interpreter/emulator for the Chip8 virtual machine written in the C programming language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:32:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can email me at sysgrammer@protonmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look at ungetc, fseek and rewind.</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/posts/a-look-at-ungetc-fseek-rewind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 09:07:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/posts/a-look-at-ungetc-fseek-rewind/</guid>
      <description>Index Link to heading The case of a few bytes Results Why is this happening? A better way to do things Bitmap File header Device-Independent Bitmap Too Long didn&amp;rsquo;t read Footnotes The case of a few bytes Link to heading I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a small hobby project/program of mine. It implements image rotation by some angle (in degrees). I chose the bitmap format to write back the image that was rotated, the input image is also expected to be a bitmap image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:54:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello to the internet!&#xA;This is just a placeholder post that I made so that my Blog isn&amp;rsquo;t empty.&#xA;Check out my github! Thanks for reading this. See ya&amp;rsquo; around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Amrit, a computer science student and a hobbyist programmmer. My interests vary from Computers to Photography, Reading, and learning new languages.&#xA;In terms of technical interests, I love working closely with systems. I&amp;rsquo;m have experience in working with C, C++, Python, x86_64. I have not found my niche in the industry and try to delve into various things. Most of my notable projects are pinned on my GitHub profile and listed on the Projects page.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
