<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amrit&#39;s Corner</title>
    <link>https://rdseed.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amrit&#39;s Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rdseed.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/notes/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/notes/notes/</guid>
      <description> PPM File Format for images </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>dy-chip8-reborn Link to heading This is an interpreter/emulator for the Chip8 virtual machine written in the C programming language. It works with the development library SDL2 to provide graphics and audio support. This project has been archived in favor of my in-development based-chip8-pp project which uses C++.
Forth86 Link to heading Forth86 is an interpreter for the FORTH Programming Language written in x86_64 assembly language. It depends on my libx86 project which provides a base for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:32:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can email me at sysgrammer@protonmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realization</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/posts/realization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 13:47:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/posts/realization/</guid>
      <description>I have been wondering why I suck at what I do, why I&amp;rsquo;m the least skilled among my skilled peers. After pondering on it for a while, I have come to realise - I simply do not do what I want, instead I chase after what I think I want which will lead me to become more skilled.
But I realise that now as I see at my past self, who got me to the point where I am today, by doing what I wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:54:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello to the internet!
This is just a placeholder post that I made so that my Blog isn&amp;rsquo;t empty. Hope you don&amp;rsquo;t mind!
Check out my github! Thanks for reading this. See ya&amp;rsquo; around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Amritpal Singh, a soon-to-be to be Computer Science student. My interests vary from Computers to Photography, Reading, Cooking and basically anything that interests me.
In terms of the technical interests, I love working closesly with systems. I&amp;rsquo;m quite experienced in C and currently I&amp;rsquo;m trying to increase my repertoire with C++. Most of my notable projects are pinned on my github profile and listed on the Projects page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
