<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amritpal Singh on Amrit&#39;s Corner</title>
    <link>https://rdseed.in/authors/amritpal-singh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amritpal Singh on Amrit&#39;s Corner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 09:07:45 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rdseed.in/authors/amritpal-singh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Comparing ungetc with fseek for going back in a stream, a few bits on BMP format</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/posts/bmp-primer-ungetc-fseek-compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 09:07:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/posts/bmp-primer-ungetc-fseek-compare/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a small hobby project/program of mine. It implements image rotation by some angle (in degrees). I chose the bitmap format to write back the image that was rotated, the input image is also expected to be a bitmap image.
Anyhow, while parsing I realised that the bitmap file header begins with a 2 byte type number that identifies the BMP and DIB header. It is commonly 0x424d (BM in ascii, 0x4d42 in little endian, how it shall appear on my machine and probably yours as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realization</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/posts/realization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 13:47:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/posts/realization/</guid>
      <description>I have been wondering why I suck at what I do, why I&amp;rsquo;m the least skilled among my skilled peers. After pondering on it for a while, I have come to realise - I simply do not do what I want, instead I chase after what I think I want which will lead me to become more skilled.
But I realise that now as I see at my past self, who got me to the point where I am today, by doing what I wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://rdseed.in/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:54:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rdseed.in/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello to the internet!
This is just a placeholder post that I made so that my Blog isn&amp;rsquo;t empty. Hope you don&amp;rsquo;t mind!
Check out my github! Thanks for reading this. See ya&amp;rsquo; around.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
